<databaseChangeLog xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:ext="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog-ext"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.0.xsd
    http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog-ext http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-ext.xsd">


    <changeSet id="007_2015_data" author="Carlus">
    	<comment>Adding data from 2015</comment>
<!-- USER -->
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 101, 'chase.bolen@gmail.com', 'Chase', 'Bolen', 'chase.bolen@gmail.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 102, 'dschoutens@gmail.com', 'Dave', 'Schoutens', 'dschoutens@gmail.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 103, 'dulimarh@cis.gvsu.edu', 'Hans', 'Dulimarta', 'dulimarh@cis.gvsu.edu', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 104, 'kdecline@gmail.com', 'Kendrick', 'Cline', 'kdecline@gmail.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 105, 'wayne.lovely@gmail.com', 'Wayne', 'Lovely', 'wayne.lovely@gmail.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 106, 'ahaaf@google.com', 'Andy', 'Haaf', 'ahaaf@google.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 107, 'Danielle.cimek@gfs.com', 'Danielle', 'Cimek', 'Danielle.cimek@gfs.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 109, 'davek@spinance.com', 'David', 'Keenan', 'davek@spinance.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 110, 'jeff.johnson@gfs.com', 'Jeff', 'Johnson', 'jeff.johnson@gfs.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 111, 'adam@birdhousehq.com', 'Adam', 'Milgrom', 'adam@birdhousehq.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 112, 'apowell@ostusa.com', 'Andrew J.', 'Powell', 'apowell@ostusa.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 113, 'carlushenry@sagetech-llc.com', 'Carlus', 'Henry', 'carlushenry@sagetech-llc.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 114, 'kovach.jc@gmail.com', 'Josh', 'Kovach', 'kovach.jc@gmail.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 115, 'kamronkennedy@gmail.com', 'Kamron', 'Kennedy', 'kamronkennedy@gmail.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 116, 'mac.fowler@modustri.com', 'Mac', 'Fowler', 'mac.fowler@modustri.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 117, 'Tim.Wondergem@priorityhealth.com', 'Tim', 'Wondergem', 'Tim.Wondergem@priorityhealth.com', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 118, 'michael.ply@spectrumhealth.org', 'Mike', 'Ply', 'michael.ply@spectrumhealth.org', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 120, 'empty presenter', '', '', '', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.user (id, login_id, first_name, last_name, email_address, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 121, 'Markus.Neuhoff@spectrumhealth.org', 'Markus', 'Neuhoff', 'Markus.Neuhoff@spectrumhealth.org', current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>


<!-- COMPANY -->

<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 100,'Open Systems Technologies','Open Systems Technologies';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 101,'Grand Valley State University','Grand Valley State University';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 102,'Maestro LLC','Maestro LLC';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 103,'Google, Inc.','Google, Inc.';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 104,'Gordon Food Sevice','Gordon Food Sevice';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 105,'SpinDance','SpinDance';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 106,'Birdhouse for Autism','Birdhouse for Autism';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 107,'Collective Idea','Collective Idea';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 108,'Modustri','Modustri';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 109,'Spectrum Health','Spectrum Health';</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.company (id, name, short_desc) select 110,'BravoLT','BravoLT';</sql>



<!-- PRESENTER -->
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 101,101,'When not trying to avert mayhem at the hands of his two boys, Chase Bolen is sometimes involved in software development at Open Systems Technologies.',100;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 102,102,'Dave is a software developer at BravoLT.',110;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 103,103,'Dr. Hans Dulimarta joined the School of Computing and Information System at GVSU in 2002. He is currently an associate professor whose teaching assignments include CS1, CS2, and Computer Graphics. His interest in Android programming motivated him to purchase the G1 Android Developer Phone, and has been developing on Android since then, but using newer devices. In the last several Winter semesters, he also taught a special section of CS2 course for students interested in Android development. Under his guidance, students from this section have published several apps to the Google Play Store. ',102;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 104,104,'Kendrick Cline is a rising Senior at Western Michigan University.  Filled with passion for innovation, working for Mobile Agility on their back-end infrastructure fits his mold perfectly.  Kendrick has been leveraging the Spring framework to support back-ends for over a year, from hackathons to production systems.  In his own time he is building Android apps overnight and learning modern practices in software development.',null;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 105,105,'Wayne has been in software development for 20 years. He holds a B.S. in Computer Science from Western Michigan University. Wayne is currently Vice President of Technology at Maestro LLC. He resides in Kalamazoo, MI with his wife and two children. When not writing code or mentoring younger developers, Wayne attempts to create sounds on the guitar that vaguely resemble music.',103;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 106,106,'Andy Haaf is a Senior Solutions Engineer and Evangelist at Google for Work. Andy has spent the past seven years helping organizations such as Gordon Food Service, RR Donnelley, Briggs and Stratton, Motorola Mobility, Brady Corporation and many others transform not only their approach to embracing technology, but the culture and tone they set for their employees. Prior to Google Andy held similar positions at Postini, Adobe Systems and WebMethods.',104;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 107,107,'Danielle Cimek is Team Manager for the End Point and Collaboration team at Gordon Food Sevice. Within this role, Danielle''s team is responsible for desktop solutions, telecom, mobile platform, digital signage and the Google platform within the organization. She has been with Gordon Food Sevice for 7 years. ',105;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 108,108,'',null;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 109,109,'I am currently a senior software engineer at SpinDance in Holland, Michigan. I''ve been a software engineer for 20 years, working on a wide variety of platforms and industries. For the last 10 years I have focused primarily on mobile software development including J2ME, Brew, iOS and Android. I have a BS in Computer Science and Mathematics from Central Michigan University and a MS in Computer Science from Michigan State University.',106;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 110,110,'Jeff is the technical Team Lead for the Google platform at Gordon Food Service.',106;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 111,111,'I am the dev manager and co-founder of Birdhouse for Autism. We are a SAAS company that makes software for caretakers of children of Autism, helping them keep notes on their care, organize data, and evaluate what is working and what isn''t so that they can improve outcomes and their daily lives.   I am originally from Detroit and have a dog named Bo. I also don''t know very much about sports.',107;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 112,112,'Andrew Powell is a managing consultant in the Application Development practice at OST. His experience in application development spans more than two decades, working as an application developer, an architect, a technical writer, a public speaker, a trainer, a consultant, a manager, a designer, and a business owner. Andrew''s career has given him opportunities to worke for companies as small as his own start-ups and as large as Meijer Corporation, Amway and Farmer’s Insurance. In one shape or another, he has spent the whole of his adult life working in the application development space.  In his free time, Andrew writes fiction (his latest novel hits bookstores in September), plays competitive poker (including an appearance in the 2013 World Series of Poker), and designs tabletop games. Andrew, his wife, and his greatest accomplishments (his two children) prepare for the coming robot apocalypse from their secret lair in East Grand Rapids, Michigan.  ',101;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 113,113,'Husband, Father of six, Entrepreneur.  I love software development.  Writing software is a joy.  More than writing software, I enjoy the relationships that are created during the process.  I also enjoy building teams, meeting goals and exceeding customer expectations.',null;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 114,114,'Software developer for Collective Idea. I''ve been developing Android applications for the past 2 years, iOS for 3 years, and Ruby on Rails for 5 years.',null;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 115,115,'A fellow programmer and systems architect. I''ve designed systems from the ground up professionally and in my freelance career for a variety of companies and teams. A java developer at heart with the communication skills to discuss business rules and definitions with the stake holders directly.',null;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 116,116,'Mac Fowler is CTO of Modustri and previously VP, Engineering at Adonit. Mac helps people and teams creatively apply technology, design and culture making work easier and more enjoyable. He’s driven by a curiosity around how “work” actually gets done and the learnings along the way.',109;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 117,117,'Tim Wondergem is an Application Development Consultant who works for Open Systems Technologies.  He''s been building custom websites and applications for over 10 years.  At OST, Tim helps with many areas of software development from UX and client side programming, as well as creating restful APIs.  Tim also loves learning and applying architectural principles which currently involves domain driven design, CQRS and distributed systems.',101;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 118,118,'Mike Ply is a Manager of Software Development at Spectrum Health.  He has worked in Software Development in multiple Industries, from automotive to health care.  He is passionate about technology, specifically around how it will transform industries.',109;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 120,120,'',null;</sql>
<sql>insert into conf_admin.presenter (id, user_id, short_bio, company_affiliation_id) select 121,121,'Markus Neuhoff has been involved in IT for over 10 years spending the majority of that time driving significant projects including Spectrum Health’s patient records platform, MyHealth. Currently he is a Supervisor of Spectrum Health’s Web and Mobile Development team where he focuses on building strong teams that are able to improve the lives and health of the West Michigan community. In addition to his career at Spectrum Health, he works with Pals Student Mentors at Grand Valley State University helping to facilitate mentoring using cutting edge online tools. He has a M.S. degree in Medical and Bioinformatics, a B.S. degree in Criminal Justice, and a B.S. degree in Biomedical Science from Grand Valley State University.',109;</sql>



<!-- LOCATION -->
<sql>insert into conf_admin.location (id, name, short_desc, full_desc, parking_info, create_dttm, last_update_dttm) select 101,'Richard M. Devos Center','Loosemore Auditorium, Richard M. Devos Center','Loosemore Auditorium, Richard M. Devos Center, Grand Valley State University','Free parking is available in the Fulton Lot under the US-131 overpass.',current_timestamp,current_timestamp;</sql>

    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>
